[{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980533685,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":20244,"timeElapsed":171733},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980543164,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":9464,"timeElapsed":181210},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980550969,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":7794,"timeElapsed":189017},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980554864,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3881,"timeElapsed":192911},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980559734,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4855,"timeElapsed":197781},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980561843,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2100,"timeElapsed":199890},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980566398,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4540,"timeElapsed":204445},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980568831,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2426,"timeElapsed":206879},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980571092,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2253,"timeElapsed":209139},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980578204,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":5601,"timeElapsed":216251},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980580302,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2091,"timeElapsed":218349},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980584498,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4190,"timeElapsed":222546},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980587128,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2622,"timeElapsed":225176},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980592388,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5254,"timeElapsed":230435},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980594161,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1768,"timeElapsed":232209},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980596653,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":2482,"timeElapsed":234701},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980599231,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":2571,"timeElapsed":237278},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980601444,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":2209,"timeElapsed":239492},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980615370,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":11771,"timeElapsed":253418},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980617502,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2126,"timeElapsed":255550},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980626808,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9297,"timeElapsed":264856},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980632125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":5310,"timeElapsed":270173},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980634217,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":2082,"timeElapsed":272265},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980637397,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":3174,"timeElapsed":275445},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980638845,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":1440,"timeElapsed":276893},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980640493,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":1641,"timeElapsed":278541},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980642779,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2280,"timeElapsed":280827},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980644694,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1911,"timeElapsed":282742},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980655877,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":9634,"timeElapsed":293925},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980657879,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1985,"timeElapsed":295927},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980659864,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":1974,"timeElapsed":297912},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980661239,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":1366,"timeElapsed":299287},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980663339,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2092,"timeElapsed":301387},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980665369,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2023,"timeElapsed":303417},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980668114,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2737,"timeElapsed":306162},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980670330,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2208,"timeElapsed":308378},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980673755,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3418,"timeElapsed":311803},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980682650,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":6872,"timeElapsed":320698},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980684984,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2327,"timeElapsed":323031},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980688945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3956,"timeElapsed":326993},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980690942,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":1991,"timeElapsed":328990},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980692547,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1598,"timeElapsed":330595},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980695489,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2934,"timeElapsed":333537},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980699069,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3572,"timeElapsed":337117},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980700666,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1584,"timeElapsed":338714},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980703803,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3132,"timeElapsed":341850},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980711380,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":6350,"timeElapsed":349427},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980712988,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1599,"timeElapsed":351035},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980715104,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2111,"timeElapsed":353151},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980719162,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4042,"timeElapsed":357206},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980721003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1834,"timeElapsed":359050},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980723096,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2085,"timeElapsed":361144},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980724275,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":1173,"timeElapsed":362323},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980727316,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3036,"timeElapsed":365363},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980730237,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2911,"timeElapsed":368285},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980733489,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3248,"timeElapsed":371536},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980740941,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":6202,"timeElapsed":378989},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980744320,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3373,"timeElapsed":382368},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980746355,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2030,"timeElapsed":384403},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980748027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1665,"timeElapsed":386075},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980750703,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2669,"timeElapsed":388751},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980752791,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":2085,"timeElapsed":390839},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980756328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3529,"timeElapsed":394376},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980758221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1889,"timeElapsed":396269},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980760704,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2479,"timeElapsed":398752},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980767217,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":4757,"timeElapsed":405265},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980769436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2211,"timeElapsed":407484},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980771911,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2471,"timeElapsed":409959},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980774150,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2237,"timeElapsed":412198},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980775883,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":1723,"timeElapsed":413931},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980778060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2167,"timeElapsed":416108},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980780707,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":2642,"timeElapsed":418755},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980782546,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":1831,"timeElapsed":420593},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980784434,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":1879,"timeElapsed":422482},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980791833,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":6214,"timeElapsed":429881},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980793393,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":1553,"timeElapsed":431441},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980795311,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":1912,"timeElapsed":433359},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980796909,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":1594,"timeElapsed":434957},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980799235,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2320,"timeElapsed":437283},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980800908,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":1669,"timeElapsed":438956},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980802700,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":1784,"timeElapsed":440748},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980804418,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":1714,"timeElapsed":442466},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980806080,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":1658,"timeElapsed":444128},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980812471,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4875,"timeElapsed":450518},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980814419,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1940,"timeElapsed":452467},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980816143,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1713,"timeElapsed":454190},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980818155,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2004,"timeElapsed":456203},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980819705,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1545,"timeElapsed":457753},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980821750,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2034,"timeElapsed":459798},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980824313,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2559,"timeElapsed":462360},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980825547,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1229,"timeElapsed":463595},{"subjectID":"ms59djsxl2","prolificID":"674c9b9386635c647f38b97c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2f1e86159535b282b8c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980826681,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1130,"timeElapsed":464729}]